<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="36"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                          EXCELLENCE
BY HARRON HOMES
             HARRON HOMES
                                                                                                                                               ]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 ]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         5 Introduction
6 YOUR KITCHEN
7 Units
8 Worksurfaces & Handles
11 Accessories
12 Ovens
15 Hobs
16 Refrigeration & Laundry
18 YOUR SPACE
19 Utility Packages
20 YOUR BATHROOM
21 Standard Tiling
22 Upgrade Tiling
24 Wet Room & Accessories
26 YOUR WARDROBE 27 Fitted Wardrobes
29 YOUR EXTRAS 29 Electrical Upgrades
30 External Upgrades
31 YOUR HOME 32 Notes
34 Next Steps
             3
]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  EXCELLENCE
BY HARRON HOMES
]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ “HARRON HOMES INVITES YOU TO PERSONALISE YOUR NEW HOME TO REALLY MAKE IT YOUR OWN
We have curated an extensive range of stunning options and upgrades to really add the wow factor to your new home.
From practical options to luxury choices, classic and contemporary styles, enclosed in this brochure is everything you need to turn your vision into reality.
To ensure that we can tailor your new home to meet your needs, we will arrange a personal appointment with one of our experienced Sales Executives to discuss the available options and to finalise your order prior to the roof stage of construction.
Harron Homes is unable to offer any items not listed within this brochure. Nor are we able to alter kitchen and bathroom layouts or adjust positionings of standard fixtures and fittings.
Please note that upon finalising and submitting your Excellence Range order, full payment is required and can not be refunded.
Please note that on occasion, we may need to substitute a product for a similar alternative in the event the original is unavailable or no longer suitable. Please speak to your Sales Executive for further information.
 5
“
]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[6
 YOUR KITCHEN
Classic looks? Contemporary designs? The choice is yours! Your new Harron Homes kitchen has been thoughtfully designed to blend practicality with personality, offering space to cook, entertain and relax in style.
 ]]></page><page Index="7" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[STANDARD KITCHEN UNITS
      ASHBOURNE CRANBROOK CRANBROOK CRANBROOK CRANBROOK ROCKFORT IVORY COBBLE GREY PLATINUM SAGE STONE IVORY
ALTA ALTA ALTA ALTA
GLOSS DUSK GREY GLOSS MUSSEL GLOSS PEARL GREY GLOSS PURE WHITE
    UPGRADE KITCHEN UNITS
NEW YORK NEW YORK NEW YORK NEW YORK NEW YORK NEW YORK MATT ANTHRACITE GLOSS CASHMERE GLOSS DUSK GREY GLOSS IVORY GLOSS PEARL GREY GLOSS WHITE
       Before making your selection please speak to our Sales Executives to see a sample of our kitchen units, worktops & tiles, as colours may vary from products displayed within this brochure. 7
 ]]></page><page Index="8" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ STANDARD KITCHEN & UTILITY WORKSURFACES
A CHOICE OF 40MM PVC EDGED WORKTOPS ARE AVAILABLE WITH COORDINATING UPSTANDS
ALPINE WHITE ALASKA BRAZILIAN WALNUT COPPER SLATE DARK ASH
MARBLE SIROCO OAK BLOCK PASTEL OAK TECTONICA EVEREST BLACK
          STANDARD UNIT HANDLE OPTIONS
A CHOICE OF CLASSIC & CONTEMPORARY STYLES
HPK672 HPK751 HPK642 HPK643 HPK630 HPK631 HPK798 HPK438 HPK785
HPK752 HPK753 HPK644 HPK650 HPK634 HPK640 HPK445 HPK448 HPK784
                  8 Before making your selection please speak to our Sales Executives to see a sample of our kitchen units, worktops & tiles, as colours may vary from products displayed within this brochure.
]]></page><page Index="9" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    WORKSURFACES & UNITS
Personalise the hub of your new home from our extensive range of kitchen units, worksurfaces and door handles to reflect your own style. Manufactured by Symphony and built to last, our flexible range is sure to offer something for everyone. Choose lighting options, integrated appliances and other solutions to complete the perfect look.
9
]]></page><page Index="10" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 10
]]></page><page Index="11" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[UPGRADE WORKSURFACES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
Upgrade to a range of stunning Granite or Quartz worksurfaces, including inset sink and drainer grooves (Replacing Standard Laminate Choices)
EXTRACTION
STYLES FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
   Caple stainless steel “chimney style” extractor hood including stainless steel splashback
Larger “island style” hoods are included where applicable - please refer to specific kitchen layout for details
UPGRADE TO GLASS SPLASHBACKS (REPLACING STAINLESS STEEL)
  BLACK PEWTER
SINK & TAP
STYLES FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
  Franke stainless steel sink and complimentary Hansgrohe “Focus” mixer taps
UPGRADE LIGHTING
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
  Grace Under Unit Lighting Arezzo Under Unit Lighting
  LED Strip Worksurface Lighting Plinth Lighting
  11
]]></page><page Index="12" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 12
OVEN
INCLUDED IN THE HARRON HOMES SPECIFICATION INCLUDED IN SUPERIOR & PREMIUM LEVEL HOMES
ZANUSSI SINGLE OVEN MULTIFUNCTION OVEN
Incorporating 5 functions. Rotary controls, Fully programmable timer, catalytic liners, White LEDs, Antifingerprint Stainless steel
INCLUDED IN EXECUTIVE LEVEL HOMES
ZANUSSI BUILT IN DOUBLE OVEN
Incorporating 2 main oven functions and 5 top oven functions. Fully programmable timer. Clean ‘n’ Clear enamel liners. White LEDs, Antifingerprint Stainless Steel
  UPGRADE OVEN
AVAILABLE FOR SUPERIOR & PREMIUM LEVEL HOMES
ZANUSSI BUILT UNDER DOUBLE OVEN (REPLACING BUILT UNDER SINGLE OVEN)
Incorporating 2 main oven functions and 5 top oven functions. Fully programmable timer. Clean ‘n’ Clear enamel liners. White LEDs, Antifingerprint Stainless Steel
   Quality built in cooking appliances are included in your new home, upgrade to include additional refrigeration and laundry appliances for added convenience.
 ]]></page><page Index="13" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ 13
]]></page><page Index="14" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  “
THE KITCHEN IS THE HEART OF THE HOME
“
]]></page><page Index="15" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ HOBS
INCLUDED IN THE HARRON HOMES SPECIFICATION
INCLUDED IN SUPERIOR & PREMIUM LEVEL HOMES
ZANUSSI 4 BURNER GAS HOB
Stainless Steel, 60cm wide 4 burner gas hob. Side rotary controls. Enamel pan supports. Flame safety device
INCLUDED IN EXECUTIVE LEVEL HOMES
ZANUSSI 5 BURNER GAS HOB
Stainless Steel, 75cm wide 5 burner gas hob with triple crown burner. Enamel pan supports. Flame safety device
  UPGRADE HOBS
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
  UPGRADE TO 5 BURNER GAS HOB (Replacing 4 Burner Gas Hob) Available on selected house types only
UPGRADE TO ZANUSSI 60CM 4 ZONE
Frameless Ceramic Hob With Touch Controls. (Replacing Standard)
  UPGRADE TO ZANUSSI 80CM 4 ZONE
Frameless Induction Hob With Touch Controls. (Replacing Standard)
Available on selected house types only
UPGRADE TO ZANUSSI 60CM 4 ZONE
Frameless Induction Hob With Touch Controls. (Replacing Standard)
 15
]]></page><page Index="16" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[16
REFRIGERATION
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
  ZANUSSI IN-COLUMN LOW FROST 50:50 SPLIT FRIDGE FREEZER
ZANUSSI IN-COLUMN 50:50 SPLIT FROST FREE FRIDGE FREEZER
ZANUSSI INTEGRATED UNDER COUNTER FREEZER
  ZANUSSI INTEGRATED UNDER COUNTER FRIDGE
UPGRADE APPLIANCES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
CDA INTEGRATED WINE COOLER
Single temperature storage zone, Double glazed door, Wooden slide-out shelves, Temperature memory function, humidifier to maintain 50-80% RH, electronic temperature control, LED interior lighting, over temperature alarm
Not available in the Alderton
   ]]></page><page Index="17" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ UPGRADE APPLIANCES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
    ZANUSSI FULLY INTEGRATED DISHWASHER
13 place settings, Airdry, 5 programmes, 3hr time delay, 11ltr, 50dBa, A+
ZANUSSI INTEGRATED WASHING MACHINE
7kg wash load, 1200rpm spin speed, 3 digit LED display, 20 programmes including Denim, Delicates, Mixed and Easy iron. Energy A+++AB. White
ZANUSSI INTEGRATED WASHER DRYER
7kg wash load, 4kg dry load, 1600rpm spin speed, medium display, 14 programmes including Sportswear, Outdoor, 1 hour 1kg. Energy A. White
CAPLE INTEGRATED HEAT PUMP TUMBLE DRYER
7kg drying load, 4 drying levels, anti crease function, “rapid” programmes, sensor drying, Energy A+, white.
  17
]]></page><page Index="18" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  YOUR SPACE
If you have a penchant for organisation or are just looking for somewhere to store the everyday essentials, make the most of the space in your new utility room. Upgrade to include additional wall or base unit cupboards to match your chosen kitchen style, designed to fit perfectly in the space available.
18
]]></page><page Index="19" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ UTILITY ROOM PACKAGES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
ADDITIONAL WALL UNITS PACKAGE
A bespoke package of quality wall units designed to fill the available space on the wall of your new utility room for added storage.
Plan and included unit sizes are available to view in the sales office.
ADDITIONAL BASE UNITS PACKAGE
A bespoke package of quality base units designed to fill the available space under the work surfaces of your new utility room for added storage. Spaces will be left suitable for a washing machine and a tumble dryer with the remaining space to be filled with units.
Plan and included unit sizes are available to view in the sales office.
Please note that within the layout for the Edlingham and Hedingham styles only, allocation can be made to incorporate an American Style Fridge Freezer and upgrade to include a plumbing feed.
ADDITIONAL BASE UNITS TO REPLACE
AN APPLIANCE SPACE
Designed to replace an unrequired appliance space with additional storage capacity. Available to purchase in addition to the above Base Unit Package.
19
]]></page><page Index="20" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[20
 YOUR BATHROOM
A place to relax and unwind. Our range of stunning Porcelanosa wall tiles will help you to create a luxury retreat in your own home. Add boutique finishes from our upgrade range to complete your style or give the practical touch.
 ]]></page><page Index="21" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[      INDIC
STANDARD WALL TILING
A wide range of standard tile choices are available including the option to incorporate a feature in a contrasting tile.
Feature tile choices are available in certain tile styles and are designed to match perfectly with the main tile option. Tiles from different ranges cannot be mixed and matched. Please speak to your Sales Executive for further information.
MAIN & FEATURE STYLES
BOTTEGA CALIZA MADAGASCAR MADAGASCAR CUBICA BLANCO SHINE NIQUEL NATURAL BLANCO
MARBELLA STONE ONA NATURAL ONA BLANCO CUBICA GRIS SHINE DARK SHINE ALUMINIO
       CUBIC INDIC
STAND ALONE STYLES
STANDARD TILES WITH NO MATCHING FEATURE TILE
FEATURE TILES CAN BE ADDED IN THE FOLLOWING DESIGNS:
• The whole shower cubicle or the whole bath area (where applicable) as a contrasting feature, with the remainder of the tiling completed in the main style.
• The back wall of the shower cubicle or the long wall of the bath, (or both where applicable) as a contrasting feature with the remainder of the tiling completed in the main style.
• A contrasting feature is not necessary and each of our main tiling options can be installed as a stand alone tile with no additional feature.
    MALAGA ACERO
MALAGA WHITE
CHINA BLANCO
CRYSTAL WHITE
 Before making your selection please speak to our Sales Executives to see a sample of our kitchen units, worktops & tiles, as colours may vary from products displayed within this brochure. 21
 ]]></page><page Index="22" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[RODANO ACERO
MOSAICO RODANO ACERO
CHINA BLANCO
OXO DECO BLANCO
BOTTEGA ACERO BOTTEGA WHITE NANTES ACERO KINGSTON NACAR RUGGINE NIQUEL
SPIGA BOTTEGA SPIGA BOTTEGA MOSAICO NANTES JAMAICA NACAR RUGGINE ALUMINIO ACERO WHITE ACERO
UPGRADE WALL TILING
               22 Before making your selection please speak to our Sales Executives to see a sample of our kitchen units, worktops & tiles, as colours may vary from products displayed within this brochure.
STAND ALONE STYLES
UPGRADED TILES WITH NO MATCHING FEATURE TILE
MIRAGE WHITE MIRAGE SILVER MIRAGE DARK MARMOL CARRARA RIVOLI BLANCO
IBIZA SNOW IBIZA GREY IBIZA CONCRETE IBIZA DARK GLOSS GLOSS GLOSS GLOSS
         ‘Ibiza’ tiles are to be fitted in a brick bond pattern.
 ]]></page><page Index="23" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  “
BUILT BY HARRON HOMES, BUT ALWAYS WITH YOU IN MIND
 “
]]></page><page Index="24" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[24
WET ROOM WALL TILING
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
SUPERIOR LEVEL HOMES
Half height tiling is included to sanitaryware walls only
to cloakroom, bathroom and en-suites including a fully tiled shower cubicle where applicable.
PREMIUM LEVEL HOMES
Half height tiling is included to sanitaryware walls only to cloakroom. Half height tiling to all walls including a fully tiled shower cubicle to bathrooms and en-suites where applicable.
EXECUTIVE LEVEL HOMES
Half height tiling to all walls is included to cloakroom. Half height tiling to all walls including a fully tiled shower cubicle to bathrooms and en-suites where applicable.
ADDITIONAL TILING
Choose to upgrade the level of wall tiling in the bathroom, en-suite or cloakroom to half height or full height tiling in the tile options of your choice.
TILE EDGE TRIMS
Tiled areas are completed with white quadrant tile trims to all edges, internal corners and window reveals, chrome square profile upgrades are also available.
INSET MIRROR UPGRADES (AS PER SHOWHOMES
Choose to upgrade to include large plate glass mirrors to the bathroom, en-suite or cloakroom as shown in our showhomes. This includes upgrading to chrome tile trims around the mirror borders. Mirrors can be positioned above the bath or above the basin. Please speak to your Sales Executive for further details and sizing as this may vary between home styles.
   ]]></page><page Index="25" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ BATHROOM UPGRADES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
  SHOWER OVER THE BATH
Thermostatic mixer shower complete with full height tiling to the bath area and glass screen
CHROME HEATED TOWEL RAIL
Upgraded from standard radiator, sizes and positions may vary, please speak to your sales executive for further details
   2 DRAWER VANITY UNIT
Available to bathrooms only
CROMA SELECT S 180 CROMETTA E 240 ECOSMART WITH ECOSMART WITH
THERMOSTATIC THERMOSTATIC SHOWER MIXER SHOWER MIXER
   25
]]></page><page Index="26" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  YOUR WARDROBE
Complete your main bedroom with a stylish and practical fitted wardrobe in a style chosen
by you and fitted to perfection by Hammonds. Choose from a range of hinged or sliding door options from an extensive catalogue of contemporary high gloss, classic timber style finishes or mirrored panels. Upgrade to include additional wardrobes in the same stunning styles for other bedrooms in your home.
26 Note - range, position and size of wardrobe options are subject to home style, please speak to your Sales Executive for further information.
]]></page><page Index="27" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[HAMMONDS WARDROBES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
LIBRETTO HINGED RANGE RADLEY HINGED RANGE MODERNA SLIDING RANGE NERO SLIDING RANGE
          1
HINGED SURROUND OPTIONS Matt White
Gardenia
Light Grey
White Ash
Rural Oak
Avola White
Aragon Oak
HINGED DOOR OPTIONS Choice to match Surround Option or: Silver Mirror Panel
SLIDING SURROUND OPTION
SLIDING DOOR OPTIONS Choice to match Surround Option or: Silver Mirror
Grey Mirror
Bronze Mirror
Coconut Glass
Blue Glass
Matt Silver
2
1
2
3
     Matt White Gardenia Light Grey White Ash Rural Oak Avola White Aragon Oak
Dark Pine Light Pine Midtone Walnut Cream Gloss Cashmere Gloss Frost Gloss
MODERNA CENTRE PANEL OPTIONS AS PER ABOVE OPTIONS
27
 ]]></page><page Index="28" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   “
MAKE THE MOST OF THE SPACE YOU HAVE
“
]]></page><page Index="29" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ TV ON THE WALL PACKAGE
Single socket and aerial point including additional support for a TV bracket at high level on the wall, including a HDMI cable installation
Additional double socket behind wall mounted TV
Additional HDMI cable run installed behind plasterwork linking low to high level
ADDITIONAL LIGHTING
Additional 50w downlights finished in chrome Wiring for wall lights, 2 positions including switch Additional pendant light fitting, standard fitting Additional pendant light fitting, low energy
light fitting
Additional 1, 2 or 3 gang light switch
YOUR EXTRAS
SOCKETS/SWITCHES
CHROME SOCKETS & SWITCHES PACKAGE
Upgrade to chrome finished sockets and switches to the whole home in either polished or brushed finish.
ADDITIONAL SOCKETS & SWITCHES
Additional TV point in a choice of white, polished or brushed chrome
Additional double electrical socket in a choice of white, polished or brushed chrome
Upgrade an existing double socket to a USB socket in white
Additional double USB socket in white Additional telephone points in white
Shaver point in a choice of white polished or brushed chrome
Fused spur and switch for a fireplace Switched fused spur
Hot tub electrical feed to rear garden Mains door bell
ALARM/CCTV PACKAGES
GOLD CCTV PACKAGE: Includes 5 cameras and 8 channel DVR
SILVER CCTV PACKAGE: Includes 4 cameras and 4 channel DVR
BRONZE CCTV PACKAGE: Includes 3 cameras and 4 channel DVR
WIRELESS ALARM SYSTEM:
Includes 3 detectors, alarm panel, key pad, bell box and 2 door contacts
ADDITIONAL ALARM ACCESSORIES AVAILABLE INCLUDE:
Pet friendly detectors, additional detectors, additional key pads, panic button and garage detector (integral and detached)
29
]]></page><page Index="30" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[EXTERNAL UPGRADES
AVAILABLE FOR ALL SPECIFICATION LEVELS
      OUTSIDE TAP
Installed on either rear or side elevation
EXTERNAL DOUBLE SOCKET
ADDITIONAL COACH LANTERN WITH PIR
30 WATT FLOODLIGHT WITH PIR
Ideal for larger gardens
ADDITIONAL TUBULAR LANTERN
Static & PIR options available
REMOTE OPERATED ELECTRIC GARAGE DOOR OPENER
Single and double door options are available *Power to garage required
POWER SUPPLY TO DETACHED GARAGE
Including a double electrical socket and batten light fitting. Separate consumer unit installed, fed from the home by armoured cabling
PLUMBING AND WASTE FOR WASHING MACHINE TO INTERNAL GARAGES
EXTERNAL WIRING POINT WITH INTERNAL SWITCH
   30
    ADDITIONAL PATIO SLABBING
Packages of additional Patio slabbing are available to increase the size of the standard slabbed areas and link to the rear door footpath (subject to individual plot suitability assessment)
TURF TO REAR GARDEN
GARAGE LIGHTING
Upgrade garage batten light fitting to a 1200mm fluorescent light fitting
HOT TUB ELECTRICAL FEED
 ]]></page><page Index="31" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ YOUR HOME
Make it yours both inside and out! Choose to upgrade your outside space to suit your lifestyle, with additional patio slabbing, quality turf and feature lighting options to add the all-important wow factor.
  31
]]></page><page Index="32" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[32
 NOTES
Your choices and options are something to be carefully considered, so here is a handy space to record your selected colour choices and upgrades for your new home. You can also make a note of any questions you may have to remind you to discuss these with your Sales Executive during your personal Excellence appointment.
 YOUR KITCHEN
 YOUR SPACE
 YOUR BATHROOM
]]></page><page Index="33" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  YOUR WARDROBE
 YOUR EXTRAS
 YOUR HOME
33
]]></page><page Index="34" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                        “YOUR HOME, YOUR ‘EXCELLENCE’ Excellence by Harron Homes is the key to making your new home a place of which
to be proud and is an important part of your journey with us.
We invite you to make a personal appointment to discuss the options available with your experienced Sales Executive who will be there to help you every step of the way.
MAKE IT YOURS | MAKE IT HOME | MAKE IT ‘EXCELLENCE’
          34
“
]]></page><page Index="35" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                        ]]></page><page Index="36" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                      HARRON HOMES NORTH MIDLANDS HAZEL COURT BARLBOROUGH CHESTERFIELD
S43 4FD
BUILDING HOMES ACROSS YORKSHIRE, DERBYSHIRE & NOTTINGHAMSHIRE
harronhomes.co.uk
                                                                                                                                                             ]]></page></pages></Search>